Class of 1932 Records, 1928-1997
Smith College Archives
Class of 1932 Records
1928-1997
Smith College. Class of 1932.
RG 80 UUID:c21d96d1-7c42-4d9d-860b-ef1504bff0d0
15 boxes (6.6 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1932.
The Class of 1932 was the fifty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1932 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1932, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, financial information, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1932 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Addresses 1928-1931 (Box 2036, Folder 1)
- Class Baby 1935-1957 (Box 2036, Folder 2)
- Clippings 1929-1932 (Box 2036, Folder 3)
- Commencement 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 4)
- Commencement Music 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 5)
- Commencement Photographs 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 6)
- Commencement Speaker 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 7)
- Freshman Frolic 1928 (Box 2036, Folder 8)
- Freshman Handbook 1928-1929 (Box 2036, Folder 9)
- Groups 1928-1932 (Box 2036, Folder 10)
- Class Granddaughters undated (Box 2036, Folder 11)
- Hoop Rolling 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 13)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 14)
- Junior Prom 1931 (Box 2036, Folder 15)
- Junior Ushers 1931 (Box 2036, Folder 16)
- Last Chapel 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 17)
- Class Letters 1934-1991 (Box 2036, Folder 18)
- Luncheon 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 19)
- Class Meeting Minutes 1928-1992 (Box 2036, Folder 20)
- Officers 1928-1952 (Box 2036, Folder 21)
- Class Reunion Scrapbook 1932-1952 (Box 2036, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1933 (Box 2037, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1937 (Box 2037, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1942 (Box 2037, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1947 (Box 2037, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1952 (Box 2037, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1957 (Box 2037, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1962 (Box 2037, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1966 (Box 2037, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 2037, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 2037, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 2037, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1977 (Box 2037, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 13)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, A-B 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 14)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, C-E 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 15)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, F-J 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 16)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, K-L 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 17)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, M-R 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 1)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, S-T 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 2)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, W-Z 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 3)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies" 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 4)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies" 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 5)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies" 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 6)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies" 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 7)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies" 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 10)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, A-B 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 11)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, C-D 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 12)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, E-G 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 13)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, H-K 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 14)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, L-P 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 15)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, R-S 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 16)
- Reunions-Questionnaire, T-Z 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1992 (Box 2038, Folder 18)
- Reunions-Questionnaire 1992 (Box 2038, Folder 19)
- Reunions-Correspondence 1992 (Box 2038, Folder 20)
- Reunions-Photographs 1992 (Box 2038, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1997 (Box 2038, Folder 22)
- Reunions-Memorabilia undated (Box 2038, Folder 23)
- Reunions-Reunion Songs undated (Box 2038, Folder 24)
- Senior Dramatics 1932 (Box 2039, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1932 (Box 2039, Folder 2)
- Senior Questionnaire 1932 (Box 2039, Folder 3)
- Songs 1928-1932, 1952, 1962 (Box 2039, Folder 4)
- Sophomore Carnival 1930 (Box 2039, Folder 5)
- Sophomore Push 1930 (Box 2039, Folder 6)
- Step Sings 1932 (Box 2039, Folder 7)
- Class Treasurer's Report Book 1928-1972 (Box 2040, Folder 1)
- Class Treasurer's Reports 1981-1994 (Box 2040, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Oversize Records (Box OV)